<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Award Winning Beaches in Australia on Best Beaches In Australia</title>
    <link>https://beachesinaustralia.com/awards/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Award Winning Beaches in Australia on Best Beaches In Australia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 22:00:09 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://beachesinaustralia.com/awards/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>10 Best Camping Beaches in Australia</title>
      <link>https://beachesinaustralia.com/awards/best-camping-beaches-in-australia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 22:00:09 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beachesinaustralia.com/awards/best-camping-beaches-in-australia/</guid>
      <description>Due to the lower human population presence in Australia compared to the size of the land itself, finding a beachside camp is much easier than in places like Europe. And the climate in Australia means if you plan your trip well, you can remain in a climate that is always warm enough to camp comforably by the beach.
Explore some of the best voted options below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Best Fishing Beaches in Australia</title>
      <link>https://beachesinaustralia.com/awards/best-fishing-beaches-in-australia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 22:00:09 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beachesinaustralia.com/awards/best-fishing-beaches-in-australia/</guid>
      <description>We have awarded the following beaches or spots as the best to go to when looking to catch a fish. Just take your rod and reel, be patient, and you will be rewarded with a feed on the barbeque for the night.
The best fishing locations are:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Best Surfing Beaches In Australia</title>
      <link>https://beachesinaustralia.com/awards/best-surfing-beaches-in-australia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 22:00:09 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beachesinaustralia.com/awards/best-surfing-beaches-in-australia/</guid>
      <description>The criteria for the best surf spots is consistency of waves, size of the swell, cleanliness of the waves and accessibility for surfers. There are some famous surf spots that have been left out due to the epic paddle out and expert crew required to visit them safely.
So, with that said, the best surf spots in Australia are:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Best Swimming Beaches in Australia</title>
      <link>https://beachesinaustralia.com/awards/best-swimming-beaches-in-australia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 22:00:09 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beachesinaustralia.com/awards/best-swimming-beaches-in-australia/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to ocean swimming, not all beaches are suitable. Heavey current, tides, rip current and choppy water generally don&amp;rsquo;t make for comfortable swimming. Although some do prefer it rough. This is taken into account when creating the list of beach swimming locations.
See the best Swimming Beaches in Australia below.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
